anonymous-news.com 2019-12-23

# Privacy Policy

**Responsible for this web presentation is:**

Anonymous Media

Amalienstr. 71

80799 München

**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where potentially personally identifiable information may be requested.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Anonymous News and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Third Party: Google Adsense, Google Analytics, Amazon, Media.net, MadAdsMedia, Revcontent, Amazon.com**  
Google and the parties mentioned above as a third party advertisement vendors, use cookies to either serve ads or collect demographic data.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

http://anonymous-news.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Collection of Personal Information  **  
When visiting http://anonymous-news.com the IP address used to access the site will not be logged.

**Cookie Policy**

Anonymous-news.com does not store any cookies.

**Copyrighted Materials**

We are acknowledging copyrighted material, i.e. photos, videos and documents to the best of our knowledge. In case of copyright infringement, please contact us at

and we will delete it immediately.

**Links to third party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Author’s Opinions**

Author’s opinions on Anonymous-news.com may differ from website administration.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Anonymous News may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Anonymous News’s sole discretion. Anonymous News encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of http://anonymous-news.com then you may contact us at:
